<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>ZeroTech-Defence (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ZeroTechDefence</packageId>
  <author>LingLuo</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ZeroTechDefence</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.ZeroTechCore</packageId>
      <displayName>ZeroTech-Core (Continued)</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2608812829</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/emipa606/ZeroTechCore/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Mlie.ZeroTechCore</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of LingLuos mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2208716577

- Fixed the turret graphics and icons

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ZeroTechDefence][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Zero Tech-Defensive Expansion Pack
We don’t want to hurt anyone, but we will never allow anyone to destroy our home.
Introduction
Concentrated gas cannonball: After the explosion, it will generate a large cloud of highly concentrated poison, which will disperse in a few hours.
Poisonous gas mine: A simple trap that uses concentrated poisonous gas cannonballs to explode, releasing a large cloud of poisonous mist after the explosion
Electrostatic mine: After an explosion, an electrostatic wave is released, which can temporarily disable the surrounding creatures and paralyze electrical appliances
Decomposition barrier: a special barrier that can be penetrated by creatures, but will intercept near-ground projectiles and shock waves
Cell barrier: a special barrier that can block organisms but projectiles and shock waves can penetrate
Flamethrower: a flame launcher that can form a flame blockade net, which is easy to lose control when used in places with a lot of flammable materials
Frost Thrower: An unmanned turret that fires liquid nitrogen cannons that will cause a second explosion
Wind pressure generator: a controller that can accurately generate strong wind pressure, and requires someone to correct it
Arc concentrator: a generator that can accurately trigger a lightning strike and requires a certain amount of power to resonate
Acid Launcher: A non-lethal drone gun that can cause acute fractures caused by neurotoxins that can cause equipment to shift
Venom ejector: A drone gun that emits corrosive toxins. If the poisoned person keeps aiming, he is continuously burned
Prism turret: a drone gun that fires slow-speed prismatic shells, with a wide range of strikes, and those who are hit will lose blood at a high speed
Charged emergency gun: a weapon that needs to be charged with time. Each blow will release shock bombs, EMP bombs, and incendiary bombs in turn
Zero mortar: It can project accurately and at high speed, but the only regret is that it is unable to conduct long-range strikes.
Turret core: a turret auxiliary device that can greatly increase the durability of the surrounding zero sub-turrets
Skyfall cannon: A zero mortar landed on your base. How would you use it?


Language: Simplified Chinese
Sharing Agreement:MIT
Giturl https://github.com/LingLuo39/ZeroTech/

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>